# **Profile**

Software Engineer with vast background working in bank industry with financial systems. Specializing in Microsoft and AWS development technologies. Working at the largest private investment bank in Latin America. Advanced level in Portuguese and English languages.

# **Employment History**

#### Fullstack Software Engineer, BTG Pactual, São Paulo

July 2021 — Present

- · Developing and maintaining a Credit Engine
- · Microservices Architecture
- AWS Services (DynamoDB, S3, Lambda Functions, Cloudwatch, SQS/SNS, CloudFormation, StepFunctions, EC2, and etc...)
- C# .NET Core Solution and React.js
- Clean Code (SOLID) and Test-Driven Development Patterns
- · System integrations with REST and RESTful Architecture

#### Software Engineer, Itaú Unibando S/A, São Paulo

October 2019 — June 2021

- Developing automation solutions with C#, Splunk, and .NetFramework
- Comprehensive of Microsoft Infrastructure Solutions
- Main goal was to provide efficiency, availability and security through automation over our distributed systems
- Responsible for Itaú's digital transformation and reinventing the way our banking offices work to provide best customer experience and journey of our 12 million clients due to the challenges of COVID-19

# Junior Software Engineer, Itaú Unibanco S/A, São Paulo

April 2018 — October 2019

- · Developing solutions with .Net Framework, C#
- Tech Lead of the squad, responsible for the agile framework and best technical solutions

#### Software Developer, AtoS, São Paulo

May 2015 — May 2017

 Working with project management processes, working on agile teams with Scrum and Lean framework, developing banking solutions for financial institutions on Qt Creator IDE, programming language C++, database development on Oracle and PostgreSQL

# **Education**

# Bachelor in Information Systems, Universidade São Judas Tadeu, São Paulo

January 2014 — December 2017

#### Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/santosludev/ https://github.com/itsluucasdev